Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files II, 1975; cuid5389 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files III, 1975; cuid5390 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - AFSCME Legislation Department, 1997-1998; cuid5391 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - AFSCME Task Force for the Future, 1998; cuid5392 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Benefit Fund, 1958-1965; cuid5393 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Blue Collar Division: Leaflets, 1970-1972; cuid5394 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Chaplains Organizing Committee, 1982; cuid5395 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Employees, 1972, 1976; cuid5396 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Citywide Contract, 1967, 1970-1976, 1985; cuid5397 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Clerical Division: Citywide Organizing Materials, 1966; cuid5398 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Clerical-Administrative Division: Leaflets, 1970-1972; cuid5399 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Clippings: General, 1967-1987, 1991-1998, 2008; cuid5400 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining: Citywide Agreement Impasse, 1981-1982; cuid5401 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Union Responsibility (COUR), 1961, 1963-1964; cuid5402 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Community School Board, District 1 Elections, 1974-1975; cuid5403 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: General, 1955-1956; cuid5404 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: General, 1957-1958; cuid5405 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1959-Jun 1959; cuid5406 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1959-Dec 1959; cuid5407 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1960-Jun 1960; cuid5408 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1960-1962; 1968-1977; 1986; cuid5409 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Calculations, 1982; cuid5410 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 Charter, 1978-1979; cuid5411 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - DC 37: General/History, 1944-1945, 1965-1972, 1982; cuid5412 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Education Fund, 1970-1976; cuid5413 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Education Fund, undated, 1982; cuid5414 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fiscal Crisis, 1970, 1974-1976; cuid5415 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Forms: General, 1970s; cuid5416 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Grievance Procedures and Collective Bargaining Manual, 1963; cuid5417 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Health and Security Plan, 1970-1976, 1988; cuid5418 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Health News Daily, Jun 1996-Sep 1996; cuid5419 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Health News Daily, Sep 1996-Dec 1996; cuid5420 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Health News Daily, Dec 1996-Feb 1997; cuid5421 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Health News Daily, Feb 1997-Apr 1997; cuid5422 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Health News Daily, Apr 1997-Jun 1997; cuid5423 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Health News Daily, Jun 1997-Jul 1997; cuid5424 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1966; cuid5425 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1967; cuid5426 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1968; cuid5427 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1976; cuid5428 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Hospitals--Strikes: Clippings, 1968; cuid5429 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Hospitals Division: Leaflets, 1970-1971; cuid5430 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Housing Division: Organizing Materials, 1966; cuid5431 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Irish Heritage, 1975; cuid5432 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Leaflets: General, 1962-1966; 1970-1976; 1981; cuid5433 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets: Other Organizations, 1967-1968; 1993; cuid5434 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Leaflets: Social and Political Issues, 1964, 1971-1976; cuid5435 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets: Social and Political Issues, 1982; 1987; cuid5436 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Legislation (Public Health), 1971; cuid5437 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Local 135B (Brooklyn Museum) and 135M (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1956; cuid5438 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks), 1955-1966; cuid5439 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks): Grievances, 1956-1965; cuid5440 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks): Meeting Notices, 1958-1966; cuid5441 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Local 154 (NYC Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1963-1966, 1972-1974, ca.1982; cuid5442 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Local 188 (Municipal Examiners and Analysts), 1967; cuid5443 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1953-1959; cuid5444 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1960-1963; cuid5445 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1964-1967; cuid5446 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), undated, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5447 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Assistant Supervisors of Recreation (Oversize), 1963; cuid5448 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Baron v. Morris Case, 1963; cuid5449 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Grievances, 1956-1966; cuid5450 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Jimmy Carosella, 1990-1993; cuid5451 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Meeting Notices and Printed Material, 1965-1966; cuid5452 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Newsletters, 1965-1966; cuid5453 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Local 322 (Uniformed Sanitation Men), 1960-1961; cuid5454 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Local 371 (Social Service Employees Union, SSEU), 1958-1962; cuid5455 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), 1963-1964; cuid5456 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jan 1965-Jun 1965; cuid5457 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jul 1965-Dec 1965; cuid5458 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jan 1966-Jun 1966; cuid5459 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jul 1966-Dec 1966; cuid5460 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), 1967, 1973, 1980-1982; cuid5461 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Certification Amendment, 1998; cuid5462 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Children's Shelters, 1970; cuid5463 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Collective Bargaining, 1964; cuid5464 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Constitution and Bylaws, undated, 1961-1964; cuid5465 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Grievances, 1956-1961; cuid5466 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Grievances, 1963-1967; cuid5467 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Manual of Operations and Forms, 1957; cuid5468 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Jan 1965-Jun 1965; cuid5469 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Jul 1965-Apr 1967; cuid5470 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Minutes, 1965-1966; cuid5471 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Newsletters and Bulletins, 1963-1969; 1984; cuid5472 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Printed Material, 1962-1966, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5473 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1962-1966; cuid5474 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): SSEU Election and Strike, 1964-1967; cuid5475 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): SSEU Printed Material, 1963-1966; cuid5476 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Budget Crisis, 1962; cuid5477 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike I, 1964-1966; cuid5478 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike II, 1964-1966; cuid5479 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike (Oversize), 1965; cuid5480 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Bulletins, 1965; cuid5481 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Captain Reports, 1965; cuid5482 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Report, 1967; cuid5483 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Agreements, 1974-1976; 1980-1982; cuid5484 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Constitution, undated; cuid5485 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Family Paraprofessionals, 1973; cuid5486 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, 1957-1963, 1973; cuid5487 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, Grievances, 1957-1965; cuid5488 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, Meeting Notices, 1961-1963; cuid5489 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1962; cuid5490 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963; cuid5491 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966; cuid5492 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Minutes, 1963-1966, 1976; cuid5493 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Newsletters, 1965-1966, 1978; cuid5494 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Policy Consultation Council, 1956-1966; cuid5495 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Policy Consultation Council, Minutes, 1957-1965; cuid5496 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Printed Material, 1970-1974; cuid5497 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Printed Material, 1975-1977; 1981-1982; 1988; cuid5498 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, 1963-1966, 1971-1973; cuid5499 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, Grievances, 1964-1966; 1975; 1980; cuid5500 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, Salary Appeal Briefs, 1965-1966; cuid5501 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, UFT Challenge, 1973; cuid5502 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1958-1961; cuid5503 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1962-1963; cuid5504 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1964; cuid5505 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Jan 1965-Jun 1965; cuid5506 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Jul 1965-Dec 1965; cuid5507 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1966, 1973-1980; cuid5508 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1957-1961; cuid5509 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1962; cuid5510 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1963-1966, 1978-1979; cuid5511 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Salary Appeal Briefs, 1958-1962; cuid5512 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Program Assistants, 1960-1962; cuid5513 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1961-1965, 1976; cuid5514 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Agreements, 1958-1965; cuid5515 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, 1956-Apr 1959; cuid5516 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, May 1959-1960; cuid5517 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, 1961-1965; cuid5518 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Grievances, 1958-1965; cuid5519 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1966; cuid5520 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, 1957-1966, 1971; cuid5521 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Job Descriptions, 1961-1965; cuid5522 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Staff Committee Minutes, 1961-1963; cuid5523 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Staff News, 1960-1964; cuid5524 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1966; cuid5525 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Local 375 (Civil Service Technical Guild, CSTG), 1957-1958; cuid5526 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1959-1961; cuid5527 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1962-1963; cuid5528 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1964; cuid5529 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1965-1967, 1976; cuid5530 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1982, 1998; cuid5531 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 3, Department of Hospitals, undated, 1963-1967, 1981-1982; cuid5532 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 10, Department of Health, 1964-1967; cuid5533 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 13, Board of Water Supply, 1965-1967; cuid5534 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 14, Board of Education, 1963-1967; cuid5535 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 17, Department of Buildings, 1965-1966; cuid5536 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 38, Housing and Redevelopment Board, 1966; cuid5537 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Department of Hospitals, City Civil Service Commission Public Hearing Transcript, Mar 27, 1967; cuid5538 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Fire Prevention Inspectors, 1967; cuid5539 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Grievances, 1957-1965; cuid5540 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Minutes, 1957-1963, 1965, 1970-1975; cuid5541 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Minutes, 1981-1982; cuid5542 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Newsletters, 1964-1976, 1982, 1989; cuid5543 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5544 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Salary Appeal Briefs and Reallocations, 1957-1967; cuid5545 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Local 376 (Construction Laborers, Highway Repairers, and Watershed Maintainers), 1966-1975, 1980-1982, 1999; cuid5546 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers), 1956-1962; cuid5547 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Constitution, 1954; cuid5548 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Legislative Issues, 1953-1957; cuid5549 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Minutes, 1962; cuid5550 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Local 381 (Association of Laboratory Teachers), 1960-1962; cuid5551 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Local 384 (Board of Higher Education), 1966, 1972-1976, 1980-1982; cuid5552 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1955-1959 1961; cuid5553 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1962; cuid5554 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), undated, 1963-1966, 1972-1979; cuid5555 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Grievances, 1955-1964; cuid5556 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Hospital Strike, 1976; cuid5557 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Laundry Workers Organizing, 1966; cuid5558 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1955-1966; cuid5559 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Minutes, 1962-1963; cuid5560 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Newsletters, 1964-1966; cuid5561 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Practical Nurses Organizing, 1966; cuid5562 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1981-1984; cuid5563 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Salary Appeal Briefs, ca.1955-1962; cuid5564 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Local 436 (United Federation of Nurses), 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5565 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Local 461 (Lifeguards), 1963-1967; cuid5566 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Local 663 (New Rochelle Employees), 1965-1968; cuid5567 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Local 663 (New Rochelle Employees): Minutes, Union-City Meetings, 1966-1967; cuid5568 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees, formerly Local 154W), 1955-1967; cuid5569 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees), 1970-1976, 1982, 1991; cuid5570 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Cleaners (formerly Local 154W), Grievances, 1956-1958; cuid5571 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Cleaners, Meeting Notices and Newsletters, undated, 1961-1966; cuid5572 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Clerical-Administrative Employees, 1954-1967; cuid5573 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Clerical-Administrative Employees, Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1959-1967; cuid5574 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Constitution, 1960; cuid5575 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Dental Hygienists, 1966-1967; cuid5576 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Exterminators, 1966-1967; cuid5577 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Laboratory Helpers, 1955-1957; cuid5578 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Laboratory Helpers, Grievances, 1955-1959; cuid5579 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Materials I, 1962; cuid5580 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Materials II, 1962; cuid5581 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Notes I, 1962; cuid5582 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Promotional Course Notes II, 1962; cuid5583 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, 1955-1964, 1967; cuid5584 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees) Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Grievances, 1955-1965; cuid5585 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Job Duties Questionnaires, 1955; cuid5586 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1966; cuid5587 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Assistants, Minutes, 1958-1964; cuid5588 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, 1956-1959, 1966; cuid5589 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Certification Dispute with New York State Nurses' Association, 1958-1959; cuid5590 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Grievances, 1956-1960; cuid5591 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Meeting Notices, 1959-1963; 1991; cuid5592 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Minutes, 1954-1955; cuid5593 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Nurses, Printed Material, ca.1957; cuid5594 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, 1953-1957; cuid5595 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, 1958-1967; cuid5596 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, Grievances, 1967; cuid5597 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1958-1966; cuid5598 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Public Health Sanitarians, Minutes, 1962-1963; cuid5599 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1953-1960; cuid5600 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1961-1964; cuid5601 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Local 768 (Health Services Employees): X-Ray Technicians, 1953-1954; cuid5602 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), 1962-May 1964; cuid5603 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), Jun 1964-Dec 1964; cuid5604 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), Jan 1965-Jul 1965; cuid5605 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Local 924 (Laborers), Aug 1965-1967, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5606 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Certifications, 1959-1966, 1980; cuid5607 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Constitution and Bylaws, Membership/Dues Book, 1954; 1964; cuid5608 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, Jan 1964-Jun 1964; cuid5609 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, Jul 1964-Dec 1964; cuid5610 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, 1965-1966; cuid5611 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Grievances, 1967; cuid5612 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1962-1966; cuid5613 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Local 924 (Laborers): Minutes, 1964-1965; cuid5614 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals, formerly Local 154X), 1953-1959; cuid5615 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals), 1960-1962; cuid5616 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals), 1963-1966, 1970-1975, 1981; cuid5617 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Accounting Personnel, 1961-1966; cuid5618 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Accounting Personnel, Minutes, 1957-1959, 1966; cuid5619 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Grievances, 1957-1966; cuid5620 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1966; cuid5621 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Minutes, 1961-1963; cuid5622 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Newsletters, 1974-1976, 1981-1982; 1989; cuid5623 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Printed Material on Housing Issues, undated, 1962-1964; cuid5624 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Local 957 (Housing Authority Clericals): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1957-1965; cuid5625 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators), 1963-1967; 1970-1976; 2000; cuid5626 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Grievances, 1960, 1963-1967; cuid5627 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Local 1062 (Supervisors of Automotive Plants and Equipment), 1965-1966, 1972; cuid5628 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): County Clerks, 1965-1966, 1971-1976, 1996; cuid5629 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): Court Reporters, 1955-1966, 1970; cuid5630 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): Judicial Conference and County Employees, 1965-1966, 1980-1981; cuid5631 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Local 1070 (Court, County, and Department of Probation Employees): Laborers, 1966; cuid5632 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Local 1113 (Department of Finance), 1958, 1966, 1970-1976; cuid5633 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Local 1157 (Department of Transportation Supervisory Employees): Highway and Sewer Foremen, 1967-1970; cuid5634 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Local 1189 (Psychologists), 1966-1967, 1973-1974; cuid5635 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Local 1212 (Seasonal Park Men and Seasonal Park Helpers), 1966-1967, 1970-1971; cuid5636 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees), 1959-1965; cuid5637 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees), 1966-1967, 1970, 1975; cuid5638 (Box 52, Folder 19)